roundrockisd.org 2014-12-20

# Round Rock ISD | Privacy Policy

Round Rock Independent School District (Round Rock ISD, RRISD, or District) is committed to respecting and protecting your privacy as a visitor to our website. We will only collect, store and use your personal information for defined purposes.

The information collected during your visit is limited and only used to help us support and enhance our relationship with you. Your information may also be used to improve our services and your web experience.

Personally identifiable information is not collected or stored when browsing, reading or downloading information from our website.

We automatically collect and store: the name of the domain and host from which you access the Internet; the Internet protocol (IP) address of the computer you are using; the browser software you use and your operating system; the date and time you access our sites; and the Internet address of the site from which you linked directly to our sites.

We use collected information only to determine the number of visitors to different sections of our sites, to ensure the sites are working properly, and to help us make our sites more useful. We do not use it to track or record information about individuals.

E-mail addresses, or other personally identifiable information such as name, street address, or phone number, are collected only when you initiate communication with us via e-mail or provide us with the information when you:

  * Subscribe to a newsletter or a mailing list
  * Provide feedback in an online survey
  * Request information or assistance
  * Complete a registration form

Pursuant to the CAN-SPAM Act of 2003, Round Rock ISD will not give, sell, or otherwise transfer e-mail addresses collected or maintained by this website to any other party for the purpose of initiating, or enabling others to initiate, e-mail messages. E-mail addresses provided to Round Rock ISD for the purpose of communicating electronically are confidential and not subject to disclosure except as outlined by the Public Information Act (Section 552.137 of the Texas Government Code).

Personally identifiable information will be used only as needed to complete your requests or process your transactions. Round Rock ISD will only disclose personal information as required by law.

See also, [Governmental Relations](http://www.roundrockisd.org/departments/governmental-relations "Governmental Relations") for more on public information, directory information and the Family Educational Rights and Privacy Act (FERPA).
